
Title: Sony built that light bar into the Dualshock 4 for VR tracking
Description: According to an interview with a Sony designer, the light bar built into every PlayStation 4 controller is integral to the company's Project Morpheus VR initiative.                                                  ...
Pub.date: Thu,  8 May 2014 13:43:00 -0400

Title: Blog: Why Gachapon is the ultimate monetization method in free-to-play
Description: "You may feel something wrong here. Isn't Gachapon is exploiting psychological weaknesses regarding gambling behavior? What about providing actual fun and value for users?"                                                    ...
Pub.date: Thu,  8 May 2014 12:53:00 -0400

Title: Postmortem: Sanctum 2, by Coffee Stain Studios
Description: "We didn't manage to meet all of our initial goals, but we still had a hell of a good time, learned a lot, and made enough money so that we could continue making video games."                                         ...
Pub.date: Thu,  8 May 2014 11:39:00 -0400

Title: Bethesda explains the Elder Scrolls Online console delay
Description: Bethesda has delayed the PlayStation 4 and Xbox One releases of The Elder Scrolls Online for an additional six months, citing network integration difficulties.                                                    ...
Pub.date: Thu,  8 May 2014 10:19:00 -0400

Title: CCP blacklists four players after EVE monument is vandalized
Description: CCP Games has blacklisted four people who were allegedly involved in vandalizing a physical monument to EVE Online that the company recently erected in Reykjavik, Iceland.                                                  ...
Pub.date: Thu,  8 May 2014 09:56:00 -0400

Title: Vlambeer's Rami Ismail answers four common questions
Description: "What do you feel is the most important trait in a game developer?" Rami Ismail answers this question, and three others: "questions that I've received more often than any other."                                              ...
Pub.date: Thu,  8 May 2014 09:48:00 -0400

Title: Blog: Express yourself - Creating a ludic language
Description: "A ludic language is simply an analogy which applies concepts of linguistics to game design. We assign each type of choice a player may make in game to a syntactical object in a language."                                          ...
Pub.date: Thu,  8 May 2014 07:10:00 -0400

Title: Nintendo will launch new hardware in emerging markets next year
Description: Nintendo president Satoru Iwata has told Bloomberg that his company plans to launch new video game devices in emerging markets, starting from next year.                                                    ...
Pub.date: Thu,  8 May 2014 06:35:00 -0400

Title: One dev's Ludum Dare with his daughters: Jungle Noir
Description: "I set up a Kanban board on Trello and gave a brief explanation of the process to Hannah and Rachel. I was surprised by how efficient this made everything."                                               ...
Pub.date: Thu,  8 May 2014 05:47:00 -0400

Title: The latest Metal Gear Solid too late to save Konami's falling profits
Description: Konami saw its earnings more than halved during the last fiscal year, due in part to a heavy drop in profits from its video game business.                                                  ...
Pub.date: Thu,  8 May 2014 05:31:00 -0400
